# **Eamon Travers**

Frontend and Web Developer

Lichtenraderstr. 55
Berlin, 12049
eamon.trav@gmail.com
www.eamontravers.dev

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Web Developer — WACMN

Feb 2024 - PRESENT

Currently the primary web developer for the WACMN's modernisation programme. Creating web apps from design-stage to deployment, as well as collating data and structuring databases. Working with React, Typescript and APIs.

## **Frontend Developer**, Berlin— Freelance

June 2022 - PRESENT

Creating web apps and frontends. Daily usage of React, Next.js, HTML5, Typescript, Node.js, CSS & Figma. Design, coding, backend set–up and deployment. Special emphasis on accessibility and reliability. See my website for more.

## Non-tech work, Ireland/Germany — Various

2013 - 2022

Varied industries and roles, including working as a:

Programme Coordinator, Production Manager, Audio Engineer, Composer & Music Director. See full details on my site.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **IBM Frontend Developer Specialization**

2024

Average grade of 94.6% over 11 modules. See course & results breakdown here.

## Google UX Specialization

2024

Average grade of 93.8% over 7 modules. See course and results breakdown here.

# BA Double Hons - Mathematics & Music Tech.

2012 - 2016 - MAYNOOTH UNIVERSITY

Graduated with a grade of First Class Honors. Results available on request.

#### **SKILLS**

React · Javascript · Typescript · HTML5 · CSS · SCSS · Python · Git · Node.js · SQL · ORM · Next.js · Redux · Tailwind · Bootstrap · UI/UX Design

Communication &
Collaboration • Self-Drive •
Problem Solving • Creativity •
Pragmatism • Fast Learning

#### BIO

I'm a focused and consistent worker who takes pride from setting and achieving new goals. My goal is to be working as a Fullstack dev within 5 years. When I'm not coding I'm an avid musician, chess player and global affairs follower. Originally from Ireland, born in '95, moved to Berlin in 2020.

### **LANGUAGES**

**English: Native** 

German: B2 (C1 written)

Spanish: A2